Here’s The Emperor’s New Clothes by Hans Christian Andersen.
Once upon a time, an emperor liked clothes very much.
He wanted to buy some new clothes.
Two brothers came and lied to him,
“We can make wonderful clothes!
But only clever people can see them!”
They pretended to make the clothes.
The emperor’s officials couldn’t see the clothes,
but they said, “What lovely clothes!”
The emperor couldn’t see anything either,
but he said, “They’re beautiful!”
No one wanted to look silly.
The emperor decided to show everyone his new clothes.
People in the street praised them.
They were afraid to look silly too!
Suddenly, a boy shouted,
“Look! The emperor has no clothes on!”
Everyone looked at one another.
They started laughing.
The end! Did you like the story?
Please tell me what you think!